Adrian Borzyszkowski



Email adrbor@utu.fi

Phone

+358 44 981 7039

Born

12.10.1994, Chojnice, Poland

Adress

Rantatie 1 B8, 21200 Raisio Finland

About me

I am a 25-year-old information technology student from Raisio. I'm looking for a job where I can use my skills and continue to develop as a programmer. My main goal is to gain work experience in the field of information technology. I choose IT because problem solving and teamwork are my strengths. I'm not afraid of new challenges. I am willing to work in Turku and possibly beyond Finland.

Education

University of Turku 2015 – continues

Information technology

Bachelor and Master of Science in Technology

Student exchange – Italy, Padova ½ year 2019

Mainly courses about machine learning

Graduate 1.6.2015

Turun lyseon lukio

Language skills

Finnish Fluent English Fluent

Polish Mothertongue

Skills

Programming: During my studies I coded mainly using object-

oriented languages such as Java, Python, C++, C

(mainly projects during my studies)

Basic knowledge in: Version control Git, SQL, Scrum, Kanban, CSS

Other: Driver's License class B

Work experience

Property Maintenance Myllykoti Oy, Turku 7.2014-8.2014

My assignment included rest home property

maintenance.

Salesperson Viherlassila Ky, Turku 04.2017-09.2017

04.2018-09.2018

Garden shop salesman and property maintenance

duties.